http://www.xtreemconnex.com/privacy.php

HomeLoginJoinChat
Privacy Policy
XtreemConneX has the following Privacy Policy with respect to information gathered on Web pages hosted by XtreemConneX. Such information is received by XtreemConneX the terms we and us refer to XtreemConneX.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected on the XtreemConneX Web site or submitted to XtreemConneX at any time.
Personally Identifiable Information When visiting XtreemConneX and signing up for or using XtreemConneX services, you may choose to supply XtreemConneX with information that identifies you personally. For End-Users, this information may include your name and contact information, gender, birth date, occupation and industry, shipping and billing information, credit card numbers and other payment information, behavior patterns, purchase history, and other information. For Clients, this information may include the Client's name and contact information, the Client's Web site information (name, URL, visitors per day, page views per month, description, categorization), payment information, and user comments.
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which the information is intended. Such transactions may include: administering a service, such as search, community, advertising sales, ecommerce; completing an order; replying to support requests; or contacting you if you have granted us permission to do so. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy and the End-User Agreement, we do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services we offer our Clients and End-Users or to comply in responding to subpoenas, court orders or other legal proceedings.
From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others to inform you of additions or improvements to the XtreemConneX services.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures reasonably designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Personnel who have access to our database are trained to maintain and secure all information.
How You Can Access or Update Your Information
Clients can access their personally identifiable information that XtreemConneX collects online and maintains by logging in to their password-protected account and selecting "Edit My Profile.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.
Chat Sites
Social Articles
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
© 2006 - 2020 XtreemConneX.com
